Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪إن العهد يُعتز به في كل الأوقات♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=خارج الحلقة=
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
City Lord, do you recognize this?
سيد المدينة، هل تعرف هذا؟
Lingxiang Herb?
عشبة لينجكسيانج؟
It only grows in Mobei.
إنه ينمو فقط في موبي.
Why is it here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
We found it in a batch
لقد وجدناه في دفعة
of Madam Hong's shipment.
من شحنة السيدة هونغ.
It was carefully concealed.
لقد تم إخفاؤه بعناية.
This is the raw material for Yunluo Incense.
هذه هي المادة الخام لبخور يونلو.
I've heard it causes severe poisoning.
سمعت أنه يسبب تسممًا شديدًا.
On the way of my parents to the capital,
في طريق والدي إلى العاصمة،
they were ambushed by Mobei assassins.
لقد تعرضوا لكمين من قبل قتلة موباي.
And this herb was also found at the scene.
وقد تم العثور على هذه العشبة أيضًا في مكان الحادث.
That trip to the capital
تلك الرحلة إلى العاصمة
to destroy the sacred artifact?
لتدمير القطعة الأثرية المقدسة؟
Remember.
يتذكر.
Never mention this
لا تذكر هذا أبدا
in the City Lord's Mansion again.
في قصر سيد المدينة مرة أخرى.
Everything that happened was by chance and coincidence.
كل ما حدث كان بالصدفة والمصادفة.
No one could have known it.
لا أحد كان يستطيع أن يعرف ذلك.
Yes.
نعم.
(So Yunqing's parents died)
(لذا مات والدا يونتشينغ)
(because of me?)
(بسببي؟)
City Lord.
سيد المدينة.
There's something
هناك شيئا ما
I wonder if I tell you.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت سأخبرك.
Why the hesitation?
لماذا التردد؟
Say it.
قلها.
After the physician treated Mr. Yunhao,
بعد أن عالج الطبيب السيد يونهاو،
and I escorted him out.
ورافقته للخارج.
He said something strange.
لقد قال شيئا غريبا.
Strange?
غريب؟
The physician said
قال الطبيب
Mr. Yunhao's wound
جرح السيد Yunhao
seems to be stabbed
يبدو أنه طُعن
by himself.
بنفسه.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Wan.
فان.
What did you want to tell me?
ماذا أردت أن تقول لي؟
Nothing. Let's talk another day.
لا شيء. دعنا نتحدث في يوم آخر.
I'm tired now,
أنا متعب الآن
and need rest.
وتحتاج إلى الراحة.
Alright. Get some sleep.
حسناً، خذ قسطاً من النوم.
(Mu Yunqing, I'm sorry.)
(مو يون تشينغ، أنا آسف.)
(Yu's Courier)
(ساعي يو)
Godmother, have some tea.
العرابة، تناولي بعض الشاي.
Godmother, have you heard of
العرابة هل سمعت عنها؟
a plant called Lingxiang Herb?
نبات يسمى عشبة لينغشيانغ؟
I heard it's from Mobei.
سمعت أنها من موبي.
Have you ever seen it?
هل سبق لك أن رأيته؟
Never.
أبداً.
Wan, this is my first visit here.
وان، هذه هي زيارتي الأولى هنا.
You've arranged it nicely.
لقد رتبتها بشكل جيد.
Of course!
بالطبع!
Welcome to visit often,
مرحبا بكم للزيارة في كثير من الأحيان،
Godmother.
العرابة.
I thought after Mu Yunqing died,
اعتقدت أنه بعد وفاة مو يونتشينغ،
you'd marry Qiming.
سوف تتزوج تشيمينغ.
Didn't expect
لم اتوقع
he's just putting on an act.
إنه مجرد يتظاهر.
About his fake death,
عن وفاته المزيفة
I only learned afterward.
لقد تعلمت ذلك بعد ذلك.
I wrongly accused Mr. Song before.
لقد اتهمت السيد سونغ خطأً من قبل.
Sorry, Godmother.
عذرا يا عرابة.
It's my fault.
إنه خطئي.
My son
ابني
would never do such a thing.
لن أفعل مثل هذا الشيء أبدًا.
You're right, Godmother.
أنت على حق، يا عرابة.
(Yu's Courier)
(ساعي يو)
Wan, what's wrong? Worried about something?
وان، ما الأمر؟ هل أنت قلق بشأن شيء ما؟
Be careful.
احرص.
All are Madam's favorites.
جميعهم مفضلين لدى سيدتي.
City Lord, you're acting strange today.
سيد المدينة، أنت تتصرف بغرابة اليوم.
It's Madam who usually handles these.
إن السيدة هي التي تتولى هذه الأمور عادةً.
None of your concern.
لا يهمك .
You're not married yet.
أنت لم تتزوج بعد
You know nothing.
أنت لا تعرف شيئا.
This is what married life looks like.
هكذا تبدو الحياة الزوجية
Grandfather.
جدي.
Yunqing,
يونتشينغ،
put a swing there.
ضع أرجوحة هناك.
The children will love it.
الأطفال سوف يحبونه.
Over here,
هنا،
plant two trees
زرع شجرتين
to bless the Mu family's safety.
ليبارك سلامة عائلة مو.
Place two fish tanks here
ضع حوضين للأسماك هنا
with some goldfish.
مع بعض الأسماك الذهبية.
Seeing them swimming around. How delightful!
رؤيتهم يسبحون. يا له من أمرٍ رائع!
Alright, Grandfather.
حسنًا يا جدي.
But
لكن
I should check with Wan first.
ينبغي لي أن أتحقق مع وان أولاً.
If she agrees,
إذا وافقت،
you can arrange whatever you want.
يمكنك ترتيب ما تريد.
You!
أنت!
I'm doing this for you.
انا افعل هذا من اجلك .
I'm teaching you
انا أعلمك
how to build a proper home.
كيفية بناء منزل مناسب.
Grandfather,
جدي
I'll go fetch Wan.
سأذهب لإحضار وان.
Yunhao, have you recovered?
يونهاو، هل تعافيت؟
Much better.
أفضل بكثير.
Yunhao.
يونهاو.
Feeling better now?
هل تشعر بتحسن الآن؟
Yes.
نعم.
Grandfather,
جدي
I want to stay in the villa for a while,
أريد البقاء في الفيلا لفترة من الوقت،
return after recovering.
العودة بعد التعافي.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
That place is suitable for convalescence.
هذا المكان مناسب للنقاهة.
Yunhao, are you really going?
يونهاو، هل أنت ذاهب حقًا؟
Perhaps I'll send someone to accompany you.
ربما سأرسل شخصًا لمرافقتك.
No need. You're busy with work.
لا داعي لذلك، أنت مشغول بالعمل.
I won't trouble you.
لن أزعجك.
I can go there by myself.
أستطيع أن أذهب هناك بنفسي.
I'll take my leave, Grandfather.
سأغادر يا جدي.
Go and recover properly.
اذهب وتعافى بشكل صحيح.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(We're all in the Mu family.)
(نحن جميعا في عائلة مو.)
(Why must I always be a supporting character?)
(لماذا يجب أن أكون دائمًا شخصية داعمة؟)
Have some tea.
تناول بعض الشاي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Miss Yu, try this.
آنسة يو، جربي هذا.
Thank you, Mr. Song.
شكرا لك سيد سونغ.
City Lord.
سيد المدينة.
If you are available,
إذا كنت متاحا،
could you come with me?
هل يمكنك أن تأتي معي؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(Shili Pavilion)
(جناح شيلي)
(This Mr. Song looks)
(هذا هو السيد سونغ)
(somewhat familiar.)
(مألوفة إلى حد ما.)
(Spirit Tablet of Song Zhao)
(لوح روح سونغ تشاو)
I brought him to see you.
لقد أحضرته لرؤيتك.
City Lord, do you remember who he is?
سيد المدينة، هل تتذكر من هو؟
Look closely.
أنظر عن كثب.
He was my husband, Song Zhao.
لقد كان زوجي، سونغ تشاو.
He was also your father's deputy general.
وكان أيضًا نائبًا عامًا لوالدك.
Mr. Song?
السيد سونغ؟
Yunqing, you must hide well.
يونتشينغ، يجب عليك الاختباء جيدًا.
Don't come out.
لا تخرج.
After them!
بعدهم!
Though many years have passed,
على الرغم من مرور سنوات عديدة،
I wasn't even four years old then.
ولم أكن في الرابعة من عمري حينها.
I don't clearly remember Mr. Song's appearance,
لا أتذكر مظهر السيد سونغ بشكل واضح،
but I'll never forget
ولكنني لن أنسى أبدا
his life-saving grace.
نعمته المنقذة للحياة.
You still remember all this?
هل مازلت تتذكر كل هذا؟
But do you know
ولكن هل تعلم
how we've struggled
كيف كافحنا
through these years?
خلال هذه السنوات؟
Madam, I'm sorry.
سيدتي، أنا آسف.
If not for saving you,
إن لم يكن لإنقاذك،
our family of four
عائلتنا المكونة من أربعة أفراد
could have lived happily and peacefully,
كان بإمكاننا أن نعيش بسعادة وسلام،
nor would we have lost my daughter Baozhu.
ولم نكن لنفقد ابنتي باوزو.
I didn't want to forgive you.
لم أكن أريد أن أسامحك.
But today,
ولكن اليوم،
Wan told me something.
وان قال لي شيئا.
Only then did I realize the truth.
حينها فقط أدركت الحقيقة.
Recently,
حديثاً،
I think of things from my childhood.
أفكر في أشياء من طفولتي.
Never thought a childhood mistake
لم أفكر قط في خطأ الطفولة
could cause such disaster.
قد يسبب مثل هذه الكارثة.
This makes me feel guilty every day.
وهذا يجعلني أشعر بالذنب كل يوم.
Grandfather knew it was my fault,
كان جدي يعلم أن الخطأ مني،
yet chose not to hate me,
ومع ذلك اختاروا عدم كرهي،
instead, kept cherishing me,
بدلا من ذلك، استمر في اعتزازي،
and kept me by their side
وأبقوني بجانبهم
to protect me.
لحمايتي.
They only regard Mobei as the enemy,
إنهم يعتبرون موباي عدوًا فقط،
and never blame me at all.
ولا تلومني على الإطلاق.
I can't accept
لا استطيع القبول
that all this is my fault.
أن كل هذا خطئي.
(Indeed.)
(بالفعل.)
(My husband was killed tragically)
(لقد قُتل زوجي بشكل مأساوي)
(by Mobei assassins.)
(من قبل قتلة موباي.)
(How could I blame)
(كيف يمكنني أن ألوم)
(a child who wasn't even four?)
(طفل لم يبلغ الرابعة من عمره حتى؟)
Rather than hating you,
بدلا من كرهك،
I hate those Mobei people more.
أنا أكره هؤلاء الناس موبي أكثر.
They poisoned my husband,
لقد سمموا زوجي
and made me lose my daughter.
وأفقدتني ابنتي.
I will no longer hate you.
لن اكرهك بعد الآن
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
I will live well
سأعيش جيدا
to live up to those who passed away.
للارتقاء إلى مستوى أولئك الذين رحلوا.
Madam Hong.
السيدة هونغ.
May I offer incense to Mr. Song?
هل يجوز لي أن أقدم البخور للسيد سونغ؟
(Spirit Tablet of Song Zhao)
(لوح روح سونغ تشاو)
Mr. Song,
السيد سونغ،
thank you for saving my life.
شكرا لك على انقاذ حياتي.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I'll treat Qiming
سأعالج تشيمينغ
as my own younger brother
مثل أخي الأصغر
and care for Madam Hong.
والعناية بالسيدة هونغ.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
Please accept my three bows.
أرجو أن تقبل أقواسي الثلاثة.
Dear, can you hear it?
عزيزي هل تستطيع سماعه؟
Your desperate rescue of the City Lord wasn't in vain.
إن إنقاذك اليائس للسيد المدينة لم يذهب سدى.
Madam Hong.
السيدة هونغ.
Thank you for telling me about Wan.
شكرا لك على إخباري عن وان.
It's troubled me for so long.
لقد أزعجني هذا الأمر لفترة طويلة.
About your father and mother,
عن والدك ووالدتك،
I hope you can tell Wan properly.
أتمنى أن تتمكن من إخبار وان بشكل صحيح.
Don't let her blame herself anymore.
لا تدعها تلوم نفسها بعد الآن.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
♪Winter snow waltzes before the courtyard♪
♪رقصة ثلوج الشتاء أمام الفناء♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪القصور لا ترحم♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪يتطلب الأمر الكثير من الشجاعة♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪لإعادة تتبع كل خطوة♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪همسات الذاكرة، أحلام أو وهم♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪الفراشات تتسلق الجبال من أجل الحب♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪يموت قبل الزهور♪
♪You seem so distant, yet right before my eyes♪
♪تبدو بعيدًا جدًا، ومع ذلك، أمام عيني مباشرة♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪لعبة شطرنج، مصير الصراع♪
♪I dream of standing with you, side by side♪
♪أحلم بالوقوف معك جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪إذا قابلتني وجها لوجه♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪سأموت دون ندم واحد♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪لدموعك وعناقك♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪